[
    {
        "question": "Sometimes, doctors ask us to check ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "blood pressure",
            "research",
            "an impact",
            "iron level",
            "a nickname"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "blood pressure"
    },
    {
        "question": "When there's an accident, it is important that some people ............ blood.",
        "choices": [
            "go",
            "give",
            "do",
            "leave",
            "donate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donate"
    },
    {
        "question": "The verb ' ............ ' collocates with the noun 'work'.",
        "choices": [
            "give",
            "make",
            "do",
            "go",
            "talk"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "He has ............ to succeed in the next exam.",
        "choices": [
            "a title",
            "sure",
            "a desire",
            "a nickname",
            "the ability"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "sure"
    },
    {
        "question": "My sister's success ............ us to do our best.",
        "choices": [
            "decreased",
            "encouraged",
            "inspired",
            "discouraged",
            "informed"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "inspired"
    },
    {
        "question": "He donated money to build a school. The synonyms of the word \"donated\" are ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "grew",
            "gave",
            "received",
            "kept",
            "supplied"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "gave"
    },
    {
        "question": "He has a desire to help other people. The synonyms of the word \"desire\" are ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "link",
            "wish",
            "debt",
            "preference",
            "donation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "wish"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"I admire your idea.\" In this sentence, \"admire\" is a synonym of ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "praise",
            "belong to",
            "disapprove",
            "appreciate",
            "prove"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "praise"
    },
    {
        "question": "To be generous is a good quality. The antonyms of the word 'generous' are ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "stingy",
            "kind",
            "cheerful",
            "selfish",
            "disappointed"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "stingy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"I am ............ for my lost keys. I don't know where they are.\" Which of the following verbs can be used in the space to make sense?~~~",
        "choices": [
            "donating",
            "looking",
            "giving",
            "preserving",
            "searching"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "looking"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is kind of you to donate money ............ the poor.",
        "choices": [
            "with",
            "in",
            "to",
            "from",
            "for"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "from"
    },
    {
        "question": "My mother taught me ............ depend on myself.",
        "choices": [
            "to",
            "how",
            "how to",
            "what",
            "what to"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "how to"
    }
]